Guide to the Ray Lyman Wilbur, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0064A
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- 1927-1928, Series 12
  - Physics (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Physiology (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Political Science (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Psychology (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Quad (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - R (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations, letters of (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Registrar (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes Scholarships (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - S (Box 102, Folder 17)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Sororities; School of Biology; Social Service Board (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Stanford Band (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Glee Club (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - T (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Trustees (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Tuition Fees (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - U - V (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Unique (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - W (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Western School of Commercial Secretaries (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Women's Council (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - Y.M.C.A. - Y.W.C.A. (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - Zoology (Box 103, Folder 17)
- 1928-1929, Series 13
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - A (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - American (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Appointments Office (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Assistants (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Assistants (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Assistants (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Associated Students (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - B (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - B (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Bacteriology (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Bequests (Box 104, Folder 12)
  - Biology, School of (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Botany (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - C (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Chaparral (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Citizenship (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Classical Literature (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Commencement (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Comptroller (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - D (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Dean of Men (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Dean of Women (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - E (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Economics (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Education (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Endowment (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 106, Folder 15)
  - Fellowships (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 106, Folder 17)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 106, Folder 18)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - English (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - F (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - G (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - General Education Board (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Geology (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - German (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - H (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Herzstein (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - History (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - I (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - J (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Journalism (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Junior College (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - K (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Kendall, Mrs. Oscar (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - L (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Law (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Lawrence, Dr. G. A. (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Letters, School of (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Library (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - M (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - Mathematics (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - Medical School (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Men's Council (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Museum (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - N (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - National (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - O (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - P (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Pensions (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Philosophy (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Physics (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Physiology (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Political Science (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Psychology (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Public Health Nursing (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Publicity (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Quad (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - R (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Registrar (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Comm. (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - S (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - San Francisco Ocean School (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Slavic (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Stanford - Muybridge (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Rifle Club (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - T (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Trustees (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - U (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Unique (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - V (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 111, Folder 17)
  - W (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - Women's Council (Box 111, Folder 19)
  - YMCA and YWCA (Box 111, Folder 20)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 111, Folder 21)
  - Zoology (Box 111, Folder 22)
- 1929-1930, Series 14
  - A (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - American (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Anatomy (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Appointments Office (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Assistants (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Assistants (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Associated Students (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - B (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Bacteriology (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Bequests (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Biology, School of (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Botany (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Branner Seismometer Station (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - C (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Carnegie Institute (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Chemistry (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Citizenship (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Classical Literature (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Commencement (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Comptroller (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Comptroller (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Comptroller (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Comptroller (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - D (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Dean of Men (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Dean of Women (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Dormitories (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - E (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Economics (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Education (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Encina Hall (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Endowment (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Engineering Education (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Civil Engineering (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Electrical Engineering (Box 114, Folder 15)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 114, Folder 16)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 114, Folder 17)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 114, Folder 18)
  - Mining and Metallurgy (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - English (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - F (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Fellowships - Foreign (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Fraternities (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - G (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - General Education Board (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Geology (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - German (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - History (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - I (Box 115, Folder 18)
  - J (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Journalism (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - K (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - L (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Labor Relations (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Law (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Lane medical Lectures (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Letters, School of (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Library (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - M (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Mathematics (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Medical School, Sept. (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Medical School, Oct. (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Medical School, Nov. (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Medical School, Dec. (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Medical School, Jan. (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Medical School, Feb. (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Medical School, Mar. (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Medical School, Apr. (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Medical School, May (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Medical School, June (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Medical School, July (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Medical School, Aug. (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Memorial Church (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Men's Council (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Museum (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - N (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - National (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - O (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - P - Q (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Pensions (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Philosophy (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Physical Education: Encina (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Physical Education: Roble (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Physics (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Physiology (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Political Science (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Psychology (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Public Health Nursing (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Publicity (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Quad (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - R (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Registrar (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Research Survey Committee (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Research Survey - Engineering (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Research Survey - Engineering (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Research Survey - School of Letters (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Research Survey - Physical Sciences (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Research Survey - Biology (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - Research Survey - School of Medicine (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Research Survey - School of Hygiene and Physical Ed. (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Research Survey - Social Sciences (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Research (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Research (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Comm. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - S (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - S (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Ocean School (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Slavic (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Sororities (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - T (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Trustees (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - U (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Unique (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - V (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - W (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Western School for Commercial Secretaries (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Women's Council (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - YMCA and YWCA (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Zoology (Box 120, Folder 8)
- 1930-1931, Series 2
  - A (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - American (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Anatomy (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Appointments Office (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Assistants (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Assistants (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Assistants (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Associated Students (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - B (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Bacteriology (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Bequests (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Biology (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Big Game Tickets (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Botany (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - C (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - C (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Citizenship (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Classical Literature (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Commencement (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Comptroller (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Comptroller (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Comptroller (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Comptroller (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - D (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Dean of Men (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Dean of Women (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - E (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Economics (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Education, School of (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Endowment (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, Mining (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - English (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - English: Public Speaking (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - F (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships, Foreign (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Fraternities (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - G (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - General Education Board (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Geology (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - German (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - H (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - History (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education, Men (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education, Men (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education, Women (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - I (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - J (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Journalism (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - K (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - L (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Law (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Letters, School of (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Library (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Library (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - M (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Mathematics (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Medical School (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Medical School (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Medical School (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Medical School: Harkness Fund (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Men's Council (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Museum (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - N (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - National (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - O (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - P (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Pacific Ocean School (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Philosophy (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Physics (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - Physiology (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Political Science (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - Psychology (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - Publicity (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Q (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - quad (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Questionnaires (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - R (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - Radio (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Registrar (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller Institute - Medical Research (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - S (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - S (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Slavic (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 126, Folder 19)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 126, Folder 20)
  - Sororities (Box 126, Folder 21)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 126, Folder 22)
  - Stanford Glee Club (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Stanford National Board (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - T (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Trustees (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Tuition (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - U (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Unique (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - V (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - W (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - West Memorial Lectures (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Western School for Commercial Secretaries (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Women's Council (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - YMCA (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Zoology (Box 127, Folder 17)
- 1931-1932, Series 16
  - A (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Alumni and Quad Secretary (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - American (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Anatomy (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Appointment Service (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Assistants (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Assistants (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Assistants (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Associated Students (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - B (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - B (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Bacteriology (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Bequests to the Univ. (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Biology, School of (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Blodgett, D. P. (Box 128, Folder 15)
  - Board of Athletic Control (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - Botany (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - C (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - California, Univ. Of (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Foundation (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Institute of Washington (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Chemistry (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Citizenship (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Classical Literature (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Commonwealth Fund (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Comptroller (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Comptroller (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Dean of Men (Box 129, Folder 13)
  - Dean of Women (Box 129, Folder 14)
  - D (Box 129, Folder 15)
  - Dramatic Council (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - E (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Economics (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Education, School of (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - Endowment (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - Endowment (Box 130, Folder 6)
  - Tamblyn and Brown (Box 130, Folder 7)
  - Tamblyn and Brown (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Tamblyn and Brown (Box 130, Folder 9)
  - Tamblyn and Brown (Box 130, Folder 10)
  - Engineering, School of (Box 130, Folder 11)
  - Engineering, Civil (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Engineering, Electrical (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Engineering, Mechanical (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Guggenheim Laboratory (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Military Science and Tactics (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, Mining (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - English (Box 131, Folder 7)
  - English - Public Speaking (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - F (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Fellowships, Foreign (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Food Research Institute (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Fraternities (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - G (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - General Education Board (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Geology (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - German (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Graduate School of Business (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - H (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Herzstein Lecture Fund (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - History (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Hoover War Library (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (men) (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (men) (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Hygiene and Physical Education (women) (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - I (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - J (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Jordan Fund (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Journalism (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - K (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - L (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Law (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Legislation (Box 132, Folder 15)
  - Letters, School of (Box 132, Folder 16)
  - Lane Medical Lectures (Box 132, Folder 17)
  - Library (Box 132, Folder 18)
  - M (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Mathematics (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Church (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Church (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Church (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Memorial Church (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Men's Council (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Museum (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - N (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - National (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - O (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - P (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Palo Alto Hospital (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Philosophy (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Physical Sciences, School of (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Physics (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Physiology (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Political Science (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Psychology (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Publicity (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Quarter System (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Questionnaires (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - R (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Radio (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Recommendations, Letters of (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Registrar (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Rhodes Scholarship Committee (Box 134, Folder 14)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 134, Folder 15)
  - Romanic Languages (Box 134, Folder 16)
  - S (Box 134, Folder 17)
  - S (Box 134, Folder 18)
  - Slavic (Box 134, Folder 19)
  - Social Sciences, School of (Box 134, Folder 20)
  - Social Sciences Research Council (Box 134, Folder 21)
  - Social Service Board (Box 134, Folder 22)
  - Sororities (Box 134, Folder 23)
  - Alumni and Academic Secretary (Box 134, Folder 24)
  - Stanford Daily (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Stanford Illustrated Review (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University Press (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Summer Quarter (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - T (Box 135, Folder 6)
  - Trustees (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Tuition (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - U - V (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Unique (Box 135, Folder 10)
  - W (Box 135, Folder 11)
  - Western School of Commercial Secretaries (Box 135, Folder 12)
  - Women's Council (Box 135, Folder 13)
  - YMCA (Box 135, Folder 14)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 135, Folder 15)
  - Zoology (Box 135, Folder 16)
- 1932-1933, Series 17
  - A (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - American (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Anatomy (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Applications for Positions (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Appointment Service (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Assistants (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Assistants (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Associated Students (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - A Survey of S. U. in Relation to Immediate Needs for Board of Trustees (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - B (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Bacteriology (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Big Game (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Big Game Courtesy List (Box 137, Folder 4)